var questions     = [

  {
    question: "What was Ash's first Pokémon?",
    answers: ["Bulbasaur","Charmander","Squirtle","Pikachu"],
    correct: 4
  },

  {
    question: "What stone is used to evolve Nidorino into Nidoking?",
    answers: ["Sun Stone","Moon Stone","Star Stone","Cobble Stone"],
    correct: 2
  },

  {
    question: "What is Ash's rival's name?",
    answers: ["Greg","Al","Mariah","Gary",],
    correct: 4
  },

  {
    question: "Besides being a fire type, what is Charizard's other type?",
    answers: ["Fighting","Dragon","Flying","He's only one type, bruh."],
    correct: 3
  },

  {
    question: "What level does Magikarp evolve into Gyarados?",
    answers: ["15","20","30","35"],
    correct: 2
  },

  {
    question: "Ghost Pokémon are immune to what type of attacks?",
    answers: ["Fighting","Water","Psychic","Flying"],
    correct: 1
  },

  {
    question: "Dratini is what type of Pokémon?",
    answers: ["Flying","Water","Dragon","Fire"],
    correct: 3
  },

  {
    question: "Where is Ash from?",
    answers: ["Pewter City","Pallet Town","Cerulean City","Viridian Forest"],
    correct: 2
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the leader of the gym in Pewter City?",
    answers: ["Misty","Lance","Morty","Brock"],
    correct: 4
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the gym leader at Cerulean City?",
    answers: ["Ash","Misty","Nurse Joy","Lance"],
    correct: 2
  },

  {
    question: "If you enter any Pokémon Center, who will you be greeted by?",
    answers: ["Nurse Joy","Nurse Jenny","Nurse Crystal","Nurse Kevorkian"],
    correct: 1
  },

  {
    question: "Uh oh! You committed a Pokécrime, who's taking your Pokébutt to Pokéjail?",
    answers: ["Officer Brock","Officer Jenny","Officer Lance","Paul Blart"],
    correct: 2
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the Elite 4 member that specializes in dragon-Type Pokémon?",
    answers: ["Lorelei","Bruno","Agatha","Lance"],
    correct: 4
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the Elite 4 member that specializes in fighting-type Pokémon?",
    answers: ["Lorelei","Bruno","Agatha","Lance"],
    correct: 2
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the Elite 4 member that specializes in ghost-type Pokémon?",
    answers: ["Lorelei","Bruno","Agatha","Lance"],
    correct: 3
  },

  {
    question: "Who is the Elite 4 member that specializes in ice-type Pokémon?",
    answers: ["Lorelei","Bruno","Agatha","Lance"],
    correct: 1
  },

  {
    question: "What is Caterpie's first evolution?",
    answers: ["Metapod","Butterfree","Caterpee","Gollum"],
    correct: 1
  },

  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a starter Pokémon?",
    answers: ["Bulbasaur", "Charmander","Squirtle","Mew"],
    correct: 4
  },

  {
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a type of Pokéball?",
    answers: ["Super Ball", "Master Ball", "Ultimate Ball", "Ultra Ball"],
    correct: 3
  },

  {
    question: "What is the final evolution of Gastly?",
    answers: ["Gengar","Haunter","Hypno","Alakazam"],
    correct: 1
  }

];
